<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GroupAlarm Manual</title>
    <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GroupAlarm Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Active conferences</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/konferenz-status/aktive-konferenzen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/konferenz-status/aktive-konferenzen/</guid>
      <description>As with ongoing alerts, an ongoing conference can be accessed via menu “Status” – “*Conference status*” – “active conferences”. If several conferences are active at the same time, one must be selected for viewing. During ongoing conferences, initiators can:
 Add a subscriber by entering a number
 Exclude subscriber from the conference by clicking the red X
 Mute (subscriber can then only listen but are themselves not heard) and unmute subscriber</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alert creation</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/alarmieren/alarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/alarmieren/alarm/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Alert creation
 General
 Units
 Text
 Coordinates
 Alert options
 Schedule
  
Alert creation The input screen “Create alert” opens, once a participant a group or root is chosen and the button “Alert” is clicked.
General: See the alert name and an optional description of the current alert.
Units: See the amount of subscribers within the amount of units that are planned for the alert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current alerts</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/alarm-status/laufende-alarme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/alarm-status/laufende-alarme/</guid>
      <description>If an alert was triggered, the “Alert feedback” screen appears. All recipients to whom an alert was sent, are included in the feedback list. Follow the alert process in real-time here.
The participant responses can be viewed immediately at the feedback view and are updated on an ongoing basis. The dialogue window (“red box”) displays a graphical overview of the analysed acknowledgements. This overview shows the amount of participants with a specific status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Info SMS</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/alarmieren/info-sms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/alarmieren/info-sms/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Info SMS
 Alert to
 Alert text
 Timed alert
  
Info SMS View the Info SMS screen by clicking the “Quick-Launch” button or via the “Alerting” tab. When messages are sent via the “Info SMS” function, it is not possible for the participants to make an acknowledgement. Therefore, the “Status” menu does not provide any feedback on the Info SMS dispatch. Unlike the SMSprio alert, the Info SMS is treated like a normal SMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scheduled alerts</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/alarm-status/disponierte-alarme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/alarm-status/disponierte-alarme/</guid>
      <description>Alerts which are not triggered immediately but are defined with a trigger time can be viewed in “scheduled alerts”. Scheduled alerts, like conferences, can only be deleted, not changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scheduled conferences</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/konferenz-status/disponierte-konferenzen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/konferenz-status/disponierte-konferenzen/</guid>
      <description>Conferences that are not to be triggered immediately, but at a later time, are entered under “Scheduled conferences”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Closed conferences</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/konferenz-status/beendete-konferenzen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/konferenz-status/beendete-konferenzen/</guid>
      <description>All conferences are listed consecutively in an endless list. As is the case with the subscriber list, it is also possible to search for specific conferences using the filter menu.
Once the conference has come to an end, a protocol is saved under “closed conferences” in the “*Status*” menu. The entire conference process is summarised in various reports, which can subsequently be sent via e-mail. The table shows the following from left to right:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Completed alerts</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/alarm-status/abgeschlossene-alarme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/status/alarm-status/abgeschlossene-alarme/</guid>
      <description>Before archived, all alerts are listed consecutively in an endless list. As known from the participant list, it&amp;rsquo;s also possible to search for specific alerts using the filter menu.
Once the alert has been completed, an alert protocol is stored under “completed alerts” in the “Status” menu. The entire alert process is summarized in various reports that can be made available for other applications and sent via e-mail. The table shows the following from left to right:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teleconference (optional)</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/alarmieren/telefonkonferenz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/alarmieren/telefonkonferenz/</guid>
      <description>Select a root, a group and/or a participant directly from the column view of the “Alerting” screen and click “Telephone conference”: . Next step is “Telephone conference” screen (“Test_Ordner_2” was selected in the following example). The conference initiator is displayed as the first participant. The telephone number the initiator wants to participate in the conference with, must be entered in the input field. Trigger the conference with defined participants immediately or later point via the “start conference” button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handout Documents</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/einfuehrung/merkblaetter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/einfuehrung/merkblaetter/</guid>
      <description>…coming soon…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Concept</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/einfuehrung/grundkonzepte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/einfuehrung/grundkonzepte/</guid>
      <description>For an easier start with eAlarm emergency and to ensure an effective alerting process, we would advise you to outline a basic scheme of your company structure. You may ask yourself the following questions:
 Which organisational/operational units exist and what is their hierarchy? What alerting scenarios do you expect and what is the following course of events? Which User should get administrative rights, who should be allowed to alert, mutate, administrate?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Landing page</title>
      <link>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/einfuehrung/landingpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hannahmm.github.io/groupalarm/en/einfuehrung/landingpage/</guid>
      <description>To access your account, visit http://emergency.swisscom-alarm.ch and log in with your user name and password.
After logging in, you will see the following page. From here you have access to all functionalities of eAlarm emergency</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>